<resources>
    <string name="app_name">67th Milestone</string>

    <string name="about_us">BML Munjal University (BMU), found in 2014 by The Hero Group and mentored by Imperial College London, has excelled in the field of academics and innovative learning. BMU is associated with foreign universities like Singapore Management University and University of Texas to fulfill its vision and offer global-approach exposure to its students. The former President of India, Shri Pranab Mukherjee, also resolute the status of BML Munjal University as one of the finest private colleges in the developing Indian sub-continent on July 12, 2017.

BMU has achieved several milestones in the field of academics, sports, annual sports, research conferences etc. BMU aims to create ethical leaders who are skilled, knowledgeable and possess life skills essential for leading organizations to heightened results. BMU is creating an enabling environment for a sustainable college life. Through collaborations with KPMG, IBM, Siemens, Hero MotoCorp and other leading companies, our students are a step forward for their future growth and development BML Munjal University hosts a flamboyant and diverse student community hailing from Jammu to Tamil Nadu that joins together to form an union in the country’s growth and development through their unique vision. The gates of the college are open for students which will amplify their presence into a vast land of opportunities. We not only excel in academics but also provide a nourishment to create an Individual and hone it’s personality to its pinnacle.

Various events have been conducted in past few years with great success. They have been a great opportunity for students to show their talent, colleges their magnificence and sponsors their branding. The students of BML Munjal University are the driving force of the University who are global-ready and wish to create a difference in the society through their dedication and talent.</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">About the University</string>

    <string name="junkyard_desc">The participants will be given random scrap material (the only inventory) out of which you have to build a working model (machine) which can perform the specified task. It’s a test of your dexterity and intuitive thought process. The competition aims to test how one quick and creative one can be at the same time and solve a problem. That’s Junkyard Wars is about.</string>

    <string name="trasure_desc">We bring you a scientific cryptic mystery and a unique adrenaline-rush experience as you try to put together the pieces of solutions to solve the puzzle and get to the final treasure. Not a pirates game, but rather a nerds playground. Have that jolt of adrenaline in you and channelize your inner Sinbad as the deadly curses and the glorious treasures surround you. Gather your spirits, open up your maps, before the treasure is found or lost forever. So, find your next clue before all the treasure goes.</string>

    <string name="virtualsm">Let’s check your Marketing Skills now! Participate in a team of 4 and invest in gold, stock market, commodity market and derivatives. After investing for 3 consecutive days, the team with highest profit wind! A game of decision making where you will be asked to closely follow the stocks and their movements to buy or sell them. So get ready to lock horns with the stock market and its uncertain rise and falls. We eagerly await your presence for the event. Get Ready to show your ‘Intelligent Investing’ skills. Brace yourself to be the Wolf of the Stock Market!</string>

    <string name="generalquiz">Think you are the smarty pants, then prove it! Get ready to brainstorm your minds, crack open some puzzles and hit some buzzers. It is not going to be easy. So flex your brainy muscles, gather some knowledge and get ready to be quizzed in a challenge like never before.</string>

    <string name="slampoetry">Have something in heart you could never express? Were your feelings ever suppressed? Do you feel something inside you is fortified? The Speakeasy Club visions to enhance the creative expression of an individual to portray using the convention of art and literature. Poetry has always been a catalyst to express varied emotions and feelings one goes along in his life. Hence the Speakeasy Club has organized a solo slam Poetry where everyone can share his wordings and poem on a given theme. This competition will test the ability of each individual who has a command on his poems. Calling out all the poets and shayars in the arena in an all-out battle. Then take this moment to break the walls and rise like a phoenix from the ashes of dead in desires. Rhyme and say whatever you want to. Break the dams and let others flow in the flood of your emotions.</string>

    <string name="aboutus1">Founded by The Hero Group, BML Munjal University (BMU) is a not-for-profit initiative offering undergraduate and post-graduate courses in management (MBA and BBA) and undergraduate courses in engineering (BTech) and commerce (BCom (Hons)). The University has been founded with the objective of transforming higher education in India by creating a world-class teaching and learning environment. The 50-acre, fully residential and co-educational university has been notified under the Haryana State Private Universities Act, 2006.</string>
    <string name="aboutus2">Named after the chairman and founder of the Hero Group, Brijmohan Lall Munjal, BMU is engaged in creating, preserving and imparting internationally benchmarked knowledge and skills to a diverse community of students from across the world. The Hero Group is a US$ 5 billion group which includes Hero MotoCorp – the world’s largest two-wheeler manufacturer.</string>
    <string name="aboutus3">BMU is mentored by Imperial College London, the 108-year old University that is currently ranked 9th in the QS World University rankings (2016-2017).</string>
    <string name="aboutus4">The campus is located at the 67th KM stone on NH-8, District Gurgaon, Haryana, about 50 km from New Delhi International Airport.</string>

    <string name="title_activity_schedule">schedule</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Tab 1</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Tab 2</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">Tab 3</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="disc1">A tyvek band will be issued after the necessary registration fee is paid for the fest.</string>
    <string name="disc2">In case the tyvek band is lost,the student will not be allowed to participate in any events till he/she gets a new band.</string>
    <string name="disc3">If the tyvek band is lost,he/she needs to pay Rs 100 for getting a new tyvek band.</string>
    <string name="disc4">Accommodation Fee is not included in the registration fee. If the student wants to avail accommodation, he/she needs to pay for the accommodation.</string>
    <string name="disc5">Prize Money for different events is subject to change.</string>
    <string name="disc6">The cancellation of the event will be on the discretion of the event organizer.</string>
    <string name="disc7">A minimum number of participants are required for the event to be valid for prize money.</string>
    <string name="disc8">Although, prizes worth will be awarded to winners in case the participation is less than the required number.No participation fee will be reimbursed once been paid.</string>
    <string name="about_the_fest">BML Munjal University is hosting its second annual techno-cultural management fest, “67th Milestone” from April 5-7, 2018. 67th Milestone is a multi-faceted program which will be hosting a wide range of cultural and technical events. Throughout its journey, it will offer a platform for artists to perform, techies to scratch their head, speed enthusiasts to get behind the wheel and fashion freaks to walk the ramp.</string>
    <string name="about_the_fest1">67th Milestone uniquely distinguishes itself by offering companies an opportunity to hold recruitment rounds for students. Students, as well as other individuals present for this promising event, will have the opportunity for a lifetime to gain inspiration and interact with eminent leaders of the industry, executives from leading business houses and achievers from their respective spheres.</string>
    <string name="about_the_fest2">With 67th Milestone only a few weeks away, every corner of the campus is eavesdropping and has some gossip about what the 67th Milestone is offering. Vivaciousness and zealousness amongst students are at its peak and they are leaving no stone unturned to benchmark the first of its kind techno-cultural management fest, “67th Milestone.” Its vision is to always strive and create the proactive experience of entertainment and magnify the strike of events, thereby the 67th Milestone has created a more superior stack stored for you on this occasion. We are immensely proud to announce you that this year there is a surprising bonanza – all events are based on the theme “TV Series” that is profound to enhance this fest’s liveliness and strike on all the unexplored domains.</string>
    <string name="battleofbandsdesc">Music doesn’t lie; it expresses what cannot be said in words, it conveys emotions which are hard to be kept and impossible to be silent upon. Battle of bands is an electrifying and dazzling display of young musical talent that will leave you spell-bound and mesmerized. BMU is ready with a paradise of the BATTLE OF BANDS.</string>
    <string name="fashioncravedesc">Bring out the “fashionista” in you and let your glamour and style set the stage on fire! Walk the ramp and make the audience go crazy with your elegance! Enthrall the audience with your glamour, attitude, style and smile. Let out and shine in the plaza of beauty of models.</string>
    <string name="btsdesc">Tap In to the rhythm and move your soul out. Want to be that dancing star you always dreamt of? Well then, Can you hear it coming? Reduce your stress, help your heart with own frame of dance moves, so get your music and your team to BEAT THE STREET @BMU. Celebrate your minds, spirit and shape with the joy of dancing. Come, join us and dance with the whole world at your feet.</string>
    <string name="rcdesc">So, come and race against your rivals and prove your machine worthy at the 67th milestone 2018 with Nitro car- A remote-controlled IC engine car race.Get ready to set the track on fire with your very own Remote controlled cars. Hit it as soon as the green pops and honestly..... if you are still in control, you are not fast enough. Line follower robot: Keep the little brat in line.. Participate in our line follower robot competition and get your little guy featured. This good for beginners.</string>
    <string name="theatredesc">By the time you thought that you were learning to act, you already learnt to act. We all are born actors. From faking a cry to get our favourite toy, to making a teacher believe that we won’t repeat our mischief again. From mimicking for proxies to acting like we are thinking hard in the examination hall when invigilator catches us exchanging actions with our friends. The one closer to the actor inside him, steals the show. For all such talented young people we have our stage set. Just feel that this is all you know and let the best of your talent be in side out, setting fires on stage.</string>
    <string name="hackdesc">The event will host the best upcoming engineers and developers from across India to create mobile, web and hardware hacks for 24 hours. Bringing in students from all over India, HackBMU is committed to encourage and kickstart a culture of innovation, entrepreneurship, and community among future hackers of India. HackBMU seeks to keep innovation in the area through hackathon and also provide a supportive environment for everyone to realize their dreams help them in developing their skills. We wish to promote Girls in Tech, so we will be having an exclusive prize for the best Girl\'s team. Also, 20% of the spots are reserved for female participants.</string>
    <string name="planetdesc">For all the inventive minds out there, we give you a platform to present your ideas on uses of Renewable energy, creating an impact in our daily lifestyle. Create, Innovate, Market and Promote your idea in front of the leading business minds of India.</string>
    <string name="pro1">BML Munjal University is hosting its second annual techno-cultural management fest, “67th Milestone” from April 5-7, 2018. 67th Milestone is a multi-faceted program</string>
    <string name="pro2">BML Munjal University is hosting its second annual techno-cultural management fest, “67th Milestone” from April 5-7, 2018. 67th Milestone is a multi-faceted program</string>
    <string name="pro3">BML Munjal University is hosting its second annual techno-cultural management fest, “67th Milestone” from April 5-7, 2018. 67th Milestone is a multi-faceted program</string>

    <string name="robosoccerdesc">Design a robot which plays soccer. The robot would compete against others in 1-1 matches</string>
    <string name="aerialdronesdesc">Sky the limit and let’s aim to reach the clouds. Come together and explore the war of new technology AERIAL DRONES. A major technical event where teams of different colleges from all over India will be a part of the new ear of racing, DRONE RACING, of 67th Milestone.</string>
    <string name="roborace">Make a Wireless/wired robot which can travel through various hurdles, deep curves and goes faster than other bots finishes the game within a short time would evolve as a winner</string>
    <string name="linefollowerdesc">The goal of the contest is to design an autonomous robot that will follow a black line on a white background. The participants must create an autonomous vehicle (ROBOT). The bot must be able to detect line and keep following it. The ROBOT which will start on the START tile and reach the FINISH tile block by following the black lines in the shortest time will be nominated the winner.</string>
    <string name="robowars">Challenge Aries for a war.Enlist yourself into the battlefield of nuts and bolts where metal bashing metal,steel smashing steel. Hardwire your bot in the ultimate showdown</string>
    <string name="BMUMasterChefdesc">Thus, BMU Culinary club brings- "Masterchef Cooking Competition 2K18" An Opportunity to bring something more to the table with a hope to inspire the evolution of cultural cuisines and show your creativity with the Limited ingredients. Contestants go through a series of challenges and elimination rounds, in order to turn home cook into a culinary master. Hone your chops, put on your apron and get into our unique BMU MasterChef contest to show off your cooking skills. And remember: an apron is just a cape on backward.</string>
    <string name="BMUPitchersdesc">Ideas are easy. Implementation is hard. The only way to do great work is to love what you do. It’s almost always harder to raise capital than you thought it would be, and it always takes longer. So plan for that. Were you always into startups? We therefore bring BMU Pitchers where you can show your talent and impress our investors and generate funds for your startup.</string>
    <string name="BATTLEOFGAMERZdesc">Playing has always been an important part so let’s give that old fashioned idea a 21 st century twist and dive deep into the depths of virtual reality as each player takes on challenging tasks and missions to help his team and himself to the ultimate prize of GLORY!!</string>
    <string name="kairosdesc">TBA</string>
    <string name="TSECSummitdesc">Can you think out of the box while colouring inside its boundaries? Can you lead the one’s flying in The Same Sky? Then you can be a Future Man. Put forward your Stranger Things and get as unique as you can. Don’t Curb Your Enthusiasm to invent new as it will support you to rise above the Billions. Start to build again from The Leftovers and emerge victorious in the Game of Thrones to be the new tycoon. Your idea can be a new Big Bang Theory and there will be more than 13 Reasons Why you succeeded, in future. TSEC Summit will have around 4 sessions and topics will be based on theme of Vision India or India 2030 and speakers will be students, politicians, entrepreneurs, corporates, bureaucrats from NCR We will be inviting and collaborating for with other colleges from DU and NCR for this summit</string>
    <string name="GrapplingTournamentdesc">Show the world what you have got with your unique techniques. Grappling tournament is a major event in the BMU fest and often excites a lot of audience. It keeps them on their toes and get ready to witness the loudest cheers from the BMU audience. Put up your attacking and defensive skills on display and get your hands on the glorious trophy!</string>
    <string name="Rihaaidesc">Theatrics have a great capability to lure us into its world of magic. Street Play, familiarly known as “Nukkad Natak” is one of its kind in leaving us spellbound with the swiftly changing scenes and live music performances. “Nukkad Natak”, a tool once used by the working class to express and to set themselves free from the established power is now an endangered art. Unlike other dramas, street play does not need a specific stage to convey its message through acting. It can be performed anywhere by instantly turning outdoor public spaces into a podium. These plays are more of a blend of social interaction displaying different perceptions on a particular topic. BMU’s own annual fest, 67 th Milestone is resuscitating this age-old tradition as “RIHAAI”. Take your stretch and come experience a street full of heart rending dramas that you will never forget. It’s our promise.</string>
    <string name="Mechathingdesc">TBA</string>

    <string name="hallsofsummer_desc">Halls of Summer is an independent Art initiative by the students of BMU, with the purpose of bringing together like (and different) minded individuals (and groups) to create raw, unprofessional art just for the sake of creating something. Providing with a safe haven for the creative yet vulnerable side of yours, we are looking have people create art using papers, colours, spray paints, lights, sounds and everything that could be used as an embellishment. The Hall will be a retreat for everyone looking for some respite from the weather, the noise, or just looking to play with the colours and their imagination.</string>
    <string name="robodesc">Technological knowledge is the core skill required to progress in today’s world. Robotics today is like IT in the 90s and has become one of the most coveted fundamental skill. Exposure to robotics through workshops and practical learning for your students will help them gain an edge over other students, enhancing their abilities. The workshop will aim at building a very strong foundation base for the skill, with enhanced logical and problem solving abilities. To register for the workshop, you can directly paytm Rs. 400/- at 9779433340 or you can pay cash to below mentioned event organizers.</string>
    <string name="iotdesc">The Internet of Things is the network of physical devices, vehicles, home appliances and other items embedded with electronics, software, sensors, actuators, and connectivity which enables these objects to connect and exchange data. IOT and Smart System development is the organizational requirement of the modern world. Throughout this workshop, our focus will be to build a smarter approach towards real life problem solving. To register for the workshop, you can directly paytm Rs. 500/- at 9779433340 or you can pay cash to below mentioned event organizers.</string>
    <string name="dancedesc">Dance your Heart out and your body shall follow. Isn’t that right? Let out your spirits and enter yourself to the gateway of heaven. Get wild and crazy. Let the body do its gracious and elegant movement to express out its soul. Tap up your feet and groove to the beats and tunes of the music. Get ready to showcase your skills with the vision of the crowd cheering to your steps. Enjoy the flow along its way. BMU is proud to announce the Solo Dance Competition where everyone is welcome to show their sassy moves &amp; steps and engulf yourself into the hidden language of our soul. Get ready to rock-n- roll.</string>
</resources>
